Bridgestone/Firestone Interview Tapes 6410 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Bridgestone/Firestone Interview Tapes
1999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Bronfenbrenner, Kate
6410 AV
6.89 cubic feet
6.9 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials, interviews.
9256783
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
M. Clark, December 09, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 24, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Bronfenbrenner, Kate, 1954; Bridgestone/Firestone, Inc.
9256783
- Braxton Chambers - Oklahoma City - Tape 1 of 1 -- 7/1/99, Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom, 1999 (Box 1)
- Braxton Chambers - Oklahoma City - Tape 1 of 1 (copy) -- 7/1/99, Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom, 1999 (Box 2)
- Terry Netherly-Tim Cottrel: Nobelsville - Tape 1 of 1 -- 7/16/99, Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom - transcribed, 1999 (Box 3)
- Ada Owen - Tape 1 of 1 -- 7/2/99, Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom, 1999 (Box 4)
- Dave Watts - Tape 1 of 2 -- 7/27/99, Not Transcribed (Box 5)
- Dave Watts - Tape 2 of 2 -- 7/27/99, Not Transcribed (Box 6)
- Tony Meyer - Tape 1 of 1 -- 7/27/99, Not Transcribed, 1999 (Box 7)
- Gary Fernandez - International Affairs - Tape 1 of 2 -- 6/16/99, Transcribed - Kate Bronfenbrenner and Ben Francis-Fallon, 1999 (Box 8)
- Gary Fernandez - International Affairs - Tape 2 of 2 -- 6/16/99, Transcribed - Kate Bronfenbrenner and Ben Francis-Fallon, 1999 (Box 9)
- Jim Cassie - Oklahoma City - Tape 1 of 2 (copy) -- 6/19/99, Not Transcribed (Box 10)
- Jim Cassie - Oklahoma City - Tape 2 of 2 (copy) -- 6/19/99, Not Transcribed (Box 11)
- Jim Cassie - Oklahoma City - Tape 1 of 2 -- 6/19/99, Not Transcribed (Box 12)
- Jim Cassie - Oklahoma City - Tape 2 of 2 -- 6/19/99, Not Transcribed (Box 13)
- Tony Carr - Oklahoma City - Tape 1 of 2 (copy) -- 7/1/99, Transcribed -- Ben Francis-Fallon, 1999 (Box 14)
- Tony Carr - Oklahoma City - Tape 2 of 2 (copy) -- 7/1/99, Transcribed -- Ben Francis-Fallon, 1999 (Box 15)
- Tony Carr - Oklahoma City - Tape 1 of 2 -- 7/1/99, Transcribed -- Ben Francis-Fallon, 1999 (Box 16)
- Tony Carr - Oklahoma City - Tape 2 of 2 -- 7/1/99, Transcribed -- Ben Francis-Fallon, 1999 (Box 17)
- Randy Gordon - Tape 1 of 2 -- 7/27/99, Not Transcribed, 1999 (Box 18)
- Randy Gordon - Tape 2 of 2 -- 7/27/99, Not Transcribed (Box 19)
- Marla Schovanec - Oklahoma City - Tape 1 of 1 (copy) -- 7/1/99, Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom, 1999 (Box 20)
- Marla Schovanec - Oklahoma City - Tape 1 of 1 -- 7/1/99, Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom, 1999 (Box 21)
- Emil Ramirez - Tape 1 of 1 (copy) -- 7/2/99, Not Transcribed, 1999 (Box 22)
- Emil Ramirez - Tape 1 of 1 -- 7/2/99, Not Transcribed, 1999 (Box 23)
- Mike O'Connor - Akron Local 7 - Tape 1 of 1 -- 6/18/99, Transcribed -- Jennifer Bloom & Ben Francis-Fallon, 1999 (Box 24)
- Mike O'Connor - Akron Local 7 - Tape 1 of 1 (copy) -- 6/18/99, Transcribed -- Jennifer Bloom & Ben Francis-Fallon (Box 25)
- Liann Ainsworth - AFL IUD & Org Dept. - Tape 1 of 2 -- 7/6/99, Transcribed -- Jennifer Bloom & Ben Francis-Fallon, 1999 (Box 26)
- Dawn Laman - Tape 1 of 1; 7/7/99; Not Transcribed, 1999 (Box 30)
- Liann Ainsworth - AFL IUD & Org Dept. - Tape 2 of 2 -- 7/6/99, Transcribed -- Jennifer Bloom & Ben Francis-Fallon, 1999 (Box 27)
- A: Ed Keyser (7/7/99); B: Liann Ainsworth (7/7/99), 1999 (Box 31)
- Jim Pope - Backup Coordinator to Sellers - Tape 1 of 1 -- Date Unknown, Not Transcribed (Box 28)
- A: Ed Keyser (7/7/99); B: Liann Ainsworth (7/7/99), 1999 (Box 32)
- Steve Sallman - Des Moines - Tape 1 of 1 -- Date Unknown, Not Transcribed (Box 29)
- Edith Marqueg - Tape 1 of 1; 7/27/99; Not transcribed, 1999 (Box 33)
- Alfredo Martinez - Tape 1 of 1; 7/26/99; Not transcribed, 1999 (Box 34)
- Larry Odum - Time Study Rep - Tape 1 of 1; 6/18/99; Not transcribed, 1999 (Box 35)
- Larry Odum - Time Study Rep - Tape 1 of 1 (copy); 6/18/99; Not transcribed, 1999 (Box 36)
- Doug Niehouse - Pittsburgh - Tape 1 of 2; Date Unknown; Not transcribed (Box 37)
- Doug Niehouse - Pittsburgh - Tape 2 of 2; Date Unknown; Not transcribed (Box 38)
- Jeff Doonebal - Des Moines - Tape 1 of 1; Date Unknown; Not transcribed (Box 39)
- Gary Marnshz - Tape 1 of 1; 6/18/99; Not transcribed, 1999 (Box 40)
- Kevin Smith: Time & Motion - Tape 1 of 1; 7/28/99; Not transcribed (Box 41)
- Terry Welch - Tape 1 of 1; 7/2/99; Not transcribed, 1999 (Box 42)
- Jackie Whitten - Oklahoma City - Tape 1 of 1; 7/1/99; Not transcribed, 1999 (Box 43)
- Jackie Whitten - Oklahoma City - Tape 1 of 1 (copy); 7/1/99; Not transcribed (Box 44)
- Paul Gnade - Local 310 Des Moines - Tape 1 of 2; 7/2/99; Transcribed - Ben Francis-Fallon, 1999 (Box 45)
- Paul Gnade - Local 310 Des Moines - Tape 2 of 2; 7/2/99; Transcribed - Ben Francis-Fallon (Box 46)
- Paul Gnade - Local 310 Des Moines - Tape 2 of 2 (copy); 7/2/99; Transcribed - Ben Francis-Fallon, 1999 (Box 47)
- Jesse Isbell - Time & Motion - Tape 1 of 1; 7/1/99; Not Transcribed, 1999 (Box 48)
- Jesse Isbell - Time & Motion - Tape 1 of 1 (copy); 7/1/99; Not Transcribed, 1999 (Box 49)
- Roger Gates - Tape 1 of 1 (copy); 6/13/99; Not Transcribed, 1999 (Box 50)
- Nevada DeVore - Tape 1 of 1; 7/27/99; Not Transcribed (Box 51)
- Oscar Sanchez - Labor Council for Latin American Adv. - Tape 1 of 2; 7/6/99; Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom & Ben Francis-Fallon, 1999 (Box 52)
- Oscar Sanchez - Labor Council for Latin American Adv. - Tape 2 of 2; 7/6/99; Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom & Ben Francis-Fallon, 1999 (Box 53)
- Oscar Sanchez - Labor Council for Latin American Adv. - Tape 1 of 2 (copy); 7/6/99; Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom & Ben Francis-Fallon, 1999 (Box 54)
- Oscar Sanchez - Labor Council for Latin American Adv. - Tape 2 of 2 (copy); 7/6/99; Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom & Ben Francis-Fallon (Box 55)
- Ken Cross - URW President - Tape 1 of 1; 6/16/99; Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom, 1999 (Box 56)
- Ken Cross - URW President - Tape 1 of 1 (copy); 6/16/99; Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom (Box 57)
- Terry Slaughter - Oklahoma City - Tape 1 of 1; Date unknown; Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom (Box 58)
- Terry Slaughter - Oklahoma City - Tape 1 of 1 (copy); Date unknown; Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom (Box 59)
- Janice Craig - Oklahoma City - Tape 1 of 1; 7/1/99; Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom, 1999 (Box 60)
- Janice Craig - Oklahoma City - Tape 1 of 1 (copy); 7/1/99; Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom (Box 61)
- John Sellers - EVP Rubber Plastics Industry Conference - Tape 1 of 1; 6/16/99; Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom, 1999 (Box 62)
- John Sellers - EVP Rubber Plastics Industry Conference - Tape 1 of 1 (copy); 6/16/99; Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom, 1999 (Box 63)
- John Sellers - EVP Rubber Plastics Industry Conference - Tape 1 of 1 (copy); 6/16/99; Transcribed - Jennifer Bloom, 1999 (Box 63)
- Ken Harvey - Tape 1 of 1; 7/1/99; Not transcribed, 1999 (Box 64)
- Ken Harvey - Tape 1 of 1 (copy); 7/1/99; Not transcribed, 1999 (Box 65)